Chris Tack chris@tackphoto.com http://christophertack.com

Profile

With over 10 years experience in photography, video & design, I would love to pivot my career into a software developer role to utilize my rapid & continually growing skillset.

Projects

SeattleTransit - Mobile-first web app created using One Bus Away API. Users can guery a bus stop near their current location & view a list of incoming busses for a specific stop. Built with Node.js, EJS, JS, HTML5

Tools Everywhere - Tool library app where users can log in and add tools they own to the sharing library. Built with Django, HTML5, CSS, Materialize

Simon Game - A take on the game Simon. Built with vanilla JS, HTML5 and CSS. The game displays a pattern that players then repeat back as the sequence increases by one each round

Technical Skills

Javascript CSS HTML5 NodeJS Express React Django Materialize Bootstrap Python Heroku Adobe CC **QA** Testing

Experience

Owner - Tack Photography - 2007-present

- Consulted with key project stakeholders with the City of Kenmore to build a photo asset library for use in marketing materials, ads & social media
- Managed the execution and creation of a series of 12 videos for the Snohomish Conservation District (scripting, video & sound production, editing and delivery)

Photographer / Videographer - zulily Inc. - 2013-present

- Consulted with internal marketing team to produce and edit video and stills for use on TV, online ads, social media and live broadcast (Facebook Live & live events)
- Establish appropriate lighting to meet shot composition needs.
- Maintained zulily brand consistency alongside featured brands.
- Partnered with stylist to develop ideas for editorial and lifestyle imagery.
- Advised senior management regarding equipment purchases to maximize available budget
- Deliver photographers feedback to elevate standards and consistency

Lead Creative, Inventory Control, Trainer - Apple Inc. - 2005-2012

- Facilitated new employee training and existing employee developmental training
- Delivered coaching and feedback to peers & managers to create team strength and unity
- Headed & mentored team of 30+ to deliver over 10,000 training sessions annually
- Simplified complex technology concepts to ensure customer & employee understanding

Education

General Assembly, Seattle WA – Web Developer Immersive – 2018

Kendall College of Art & Design, Grand Rapids MI – BFA: Photography & Graphic Design – 2007

Activities

Race Crew Volunteer / Photographer/Videographer - SkiHawks Racing Team, 2012 - Present Volunteer - Outdoors For All Foundation, 2012 - Present Special Olympics Michigan: Coach 2000-2006, Volunteer 1994 – 1999 & 2012 – Present